R.Kamalesh Sagar

UI UX Designer



Profile

I am a UI UX DESIGNER with over 1 years and 10 months and web UI designer as 11 months of front end experience and passion for responsive website design and a firm believer in the mobile first approach. Mostly I have done UI development of websites.

Personal Information

8

7 Avvaiyar Street, Manavala Nagar,Tiruvallur,602002



8807424100



kamaleshsagar.r@gmail.com

Professional skills

Html

Intermediate

Css

Intermediate

Bootstrap

Advanced

Javascript

Beginner

JQuery

Beginner

Wordpress UI

Intermediate

Photoshop

Competent

Illustrator

Competent

Figma

Competent

Employment History

UI UX Designer, Netism Soft Pvt Ltd

Feb 2020 – Dec 2021

Chrompet

- Conceived and built optimized landing pages in HTML and CSS.
- Used various technologies, including frameworks to make code repairs and optimize corporate website.
- Pitched in to assist senior developers to meet pressing deadlines during under-staffed periods.
- Designed user interface to meet client specifications and content management system.
- Completely updated and redesigned user experience for real estate company website.

Web Designer & Development, Mclene Soft May 2018 - Apr 2019 Solution

Guindy

- Website designing and developing.
- Develop a static and Dynamic website.
- Working with a team to complete the project

System Associate, Haworth India Pvt Ltd

May 2015 - May 2018

Vayalur, Sriperumbudur

- Analyzing drawing and Scheduling the workload as per planning list and ensure that the production deliveries are meeting the dispatch plan
- Manpower deploying to the work center.
- Communicating to Plant Manager regarding process delay, process deviation and status updation.
- Assigning everyday plan for production.

Professional skills

A+

Beginner

N+

Beginner

CCNA

Beginner

MCSE

Beginner

PHP

Beginner

Hobbies

- Watching Televison
- Surfing New Techies
- Dancing

Languages

Tamil

Native

English

Conversational

Employment History

- Preparation of daily production statement and raising procurement list and sent to stores
- Work order printing and dispatched the finished goods to logistics.
- Inventory handling and maintaining the stocks.

Education

B.TECH, SRM Institute Of Science And
Technology
Vadapalani

Diploma, John Bosco Polytechnic College
Tiruvallur

HSC, K.E.N.C Govt hr sec school
Manavala nagar, Tiruvallur

SSLC, K.E.N.C Govt hr sec school
Manavala nagar, Tiruvallur

Jun 2017 - Dec 2020

Jun 2017 - Dec 2020

Jun 2013 - Apr 2015

Jun 2012 - Apr 2013

Jun 2010 - May 2011

Manavala nagar, Tiruvallur

Projects

Brumley Construction, Brumley Construction

May 2020 - Jun 2020

Canada

- It is a Construction Company using Wordpress page builder (Elementor) to built the whole site to showcase the services and their projects I
- They offer some of the services based on the client requirements and it is also showcase for the customers
- Ensuring for the loading speed of the site.

TasteMeat, Tastemeat

Jan 2021 - Feb 2021

Villivakkam

- The project is for selling the meats and sea foods items to the customers using wordpress woocommerce
- We used categories based product search ,web page design, coupons and discounts of a product
- They will provide the door delivery option and shipping charges based on the location
- And i used wordpress react native template for mobile app and changed the designs based on the client requirements